let quiz=[
    {
        question:"Who is the discoverer of the hydrogen?",
        option:[
            "Priestley", 
            "Cavendish", 
            "Ure", 
            "Levizer", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the maximum concentration limit of urea for spraying?",
        option:[
            "6%", 
            "8%", 
            "4%", 
            "No such limit", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"What percentage of body weight of an adult human is contributed by muscles?",
        option:[
            "20-30%", 
            "10-20%", 
            "40-50%", 
            "30-40%", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Approximately, how many muscles are there in Human body?",
        option:[
            "206", 
            "320", 
            "554", 
            "650", 
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the most commonly found green house gas in the world ?",
        option:[
            "Water vapour", 
            "Sulphur Dioxide", 
            "Carbon dioxide", 
            "Ozone", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"  Which of the following is not a traditional source of energy?",
        option:[
            "Natural Gas", 
            "Mineral Oil", 
            "Geothermal energy", 
            "Coal", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the percentage of irrigated land in India?",
        option:[
            "45", 
            "65", 
            "35", 
            "25", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these diseases is also known as 'encephalitis'?",
        option:[
            "Japanese encephalitis", 
            "Tetanus", 
            "Dengue", 
            "Rabies", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"On what principle does the optical fibre work? ",
        option:[
            "Refraction", 
            "Total internal refraction", 
            "Interference", 
            "Scattering", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What is main ingredient of 'Bio Gas'?",
        option:[
            "Ethane", 
            "Ammonia", 
            "Methane", 
            "Ethylene", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
] ;

